GILANG HARSYA FADILLAH

Karawang, West Java, 41313 | +6281366932277 | https://github.com/harsyagilfa www.linkedin.com/in/gilangharsya | gilangharsya85@gmail.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Bachelor of Information Systems graduate from Singaperbangsa University Karawang with a GPA of 3.64/4.00. I have a deep interest as a Fullstack Developer, focusing on website development. I have experience as a website developer and administrator where I was tasked with developing the becdex.com website. I also have experience in creating 2 projects, namely creating a company profile website for CV Radja Studio Indragiri, and creating a website-based online ordering system using the waterfall method. I am a motivated individual with good communication, teamwork, and problem-solving skills. I am also adaptable to various environments and tasks, always ready to learn and face new challenges.

EDUCATION

Singaperbangsa University Karawang

Bachelor of Information Systems - Score: 3,63/4.00

Sep 2020 - Aug 2024

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Website Developer

Sep 2023 – Now

Company Profile Website for CV. Radja Studio Indragiri

- Create a UI/UX design using Figma to create a web appearance that is very elegant and easy to understand by all groups.
- Implement UI/UX design into programming code so that websites can be created using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Add several features and animations to make the website more interactive and interesting.
- Create a responsive system on the website so that the website can look elegant on all devices.

Maritim Muda Nusantara

Website Developer and Administrator

Aug 2023 – Dec 2023

- Manage and developing the becdex.com website.
- The becdex.com website was developed using the PHP programming language with the Codelgniter framework.
- Engage in active communication with organization members and interns to design and develop an engaging website. Plan content, design an engaging look and implement creative features to create a compelling online experience.
- Designing and creating content that is in accordance with the contents of the website owned by Maritim Muda Nusantara with graphic design principles.
- Manage hosting and domain for the becdex.com website.
- Improve the hamburger menu on the about page for website display on mobile devices.
- Adding Mandarin Language Features to the becdex.com website display.

CERTIFICATES AND TRAINING

•	Front End Developer - HTML	- Myskill	2023
•	Front End Developer - CSS	- Myskill	2023
•	Intensive Bootcamp React JS for Front End Development Batch 8	- Edspert.id	2023
•	Internship and Independent Study batch 5	 Maritim Muda Nusantara 	2023

SKILLS

- **Technical Skills:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Figma, PHP, SQL, Bootstrap 4 and 5, Codeigniter, Laravel, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, UML Modeling.
- Personal Skills: Creative, Disciplined, Detail Oriented, Teamwork, Effective Communication.
- Language: Indonesian and English.